1980-01-01 12:34:56 +0200|SampleAuthor|this is a sample changelog; this is another sample changelog line; ;
1980-01-01 12:37:56 +0200|SampleAuthor|this is a sample changelog; this is another sample changelog line; ;
1980-01-01 12:38:56 +0200|SampleAuthor|this is a sample changelog; this is another sample changelog line; ;
1980-01-01 12:39:56 +0200|SampleAuthor|this is a sample changelog; this is another sample changelog line; ;